[
  {
    "body": "Unheralded pair Tommy Fleetwood of England and Northern Ireland's Michael Hoey share the lead at the halfway stage of the Alfred Dunhill Links Championship in Scotland. Fleetwood, who won the Kazakhstan Open on the second-level European Challenge Tour earlier this month, charged to the fore with a nine-under 63 at Kingsbarns, one of three courses being used for the tournament. Hoey, who also played at Kingsbarns, carded a second straight six-under 66 to join him on 12-under 132. The 20-year-old Fleetwood has already earned his place on the 2012 European Tour and has now set his sights higher. \"The last couple of weeks I've had no pressure on me really. I know where I'm playing next year, which is great, and it's definitely given me confidence because there was a bit of thought of 'Can I win?' because I had been in there so many times. \"I finally got it done, so let's see if I can do it on the bigger stage now,\" he told the official European Tour website. But both men face a significant challenge from many of golf's big names with five of the top six ranked players in the world playing at the tournament, which also uses Carnoustie and St  Andrews where the final round takes place Sunday. South African Louis Oosthuizen, who lifted the British Open at St Andrews in 2010, is one off the lead after adding a 67 at Carnoustie to his opening 66 at Kingsbarns. Former U.S. Open Champion Graeme McDowell carded a second straight 67 to lie in a big group two shots back alongside  Australian Daniel Gaunt, Scotland's Marc Warren, Austria's Markus Brier and South African Jaco van Zyl. Defending champion Martin Kaymer is looming a shot further back on nine-under, while world number two Lee Westwood and current U.S. Open Champion Rory McIlroy are on seven-under. Top-ranked Luke Donald was challenging until four dropped shots in his last four holes, including a double bogey, put him back to four-under. Donald, who is hoping to become the first man to head the money list on both the PGA and European Tours, drove into the infamous Barry Burn at Carnoustie as his second round unraveled.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Tommy Fleetwood",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "England",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Northern Ireland's",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Michael Hoey",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the Alfred Dunhill Links Championship",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Scotland",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Fleetwood",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the Kazakhstan Open",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "European Challenge Tour",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "earlier this month",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "nine-under",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "63",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Kingsbarns",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "three",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Hoey",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kingsbarns",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "six-under",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "66",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "12-under",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "132",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "20-year-old",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Fleetwood",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2012",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "European Tour",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "The last couple of weeks",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "next year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "European Tour",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "five",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "six",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Carnoustie",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "St  Andrews",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "Sunday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "South African",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Louis Oosthuizen",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the British Open",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "St Andrews",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "2010",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "67",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Carnoustie",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "66",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Kingsbarns",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "U.S. Open",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Graeme McDowell",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "67",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "two",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Australian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Daniel Gaunt",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Scotland",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Marc Warren",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Austria",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Markus Brier",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "South African",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Jaco van Zyl",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Martin Kaymer",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "nine-under",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "two",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Lee Westwood",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "U.S. Open",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Rory McIlroy",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "seven-under",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "Luke Donald",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "four",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "four",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "four-under",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "Donald",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "PGA",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "European Tours",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Carnoustie",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "Brazilian driver Bruno Senna will replace Nick Heidfeld for Renault at this weekend's Formula One grand prix in Belgium. Senna, the nephew of three-time world champion Ayrton Senna, joined the British-based team as a test driver in July and has yet to race competitively for the marque. German racer Heidfeld has picked up 34 points so far this season and secured a podium finish when he crossed the line in third position at April's Malaysian Grand Prix. Senna's last race was the season-ending Abu Dhabi Grand Prix in November 2010, where he placed 19th for HRT. Remembering Senna: King of Monaco The Sao Paulo-born driver competed for Spanish outfit HRT on 18 occasions last season with his best finish of the season a 14th place in South Korea. Heidfeld, formerly of Sauber, was drafted in by Renault at the start of the 2011 season as a replacement for Robert Kubica, after the Pole suffered injuries to his arms and legs in a rally crash in February. After his rookie year with Prost in 2000, Heidfeld spent three years with Sauber before joining Jordan in 2004. The 34-year-old spent a season with Williams in 2005 and returned for a second spell with Sauber, who had be taken over by BMW, in 2006.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Brazilian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Bruno Senna",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Nick Heidfeld",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Renault",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "weekend",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Formula One",
          "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
          "Belgium",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Senna",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "three",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Ayrton Senna",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "British",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "July",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "German",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Heidfeld",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "34",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "third",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "April",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Malaysian Grand Prix",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Senna",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "season-ending",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Abu Dhabi Grand Prix",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "November 2010",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "19th",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "HRT",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Senna",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sao Paulo",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Spanish",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "HRT",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "18",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "last season",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "the season",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "14th",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "South Korea",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Heidfeld",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sauber",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Renault",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "the 2011 season",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Robert Kubica",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Pole",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "February",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "his rookie year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Prost",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2000",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Heidfeld",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "three years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Sauber",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Jordan",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2004",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "34-year-old",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Williams",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2005",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Sauber",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "BMW",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2006",
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "Russian Vera Zvonareva came from 5-1 down in the opening set to beat Wimbledon champion Petra Kvitova 7-6 6-0 in the semifinals of the WTA  tournament in Tokyo Friday. Zvonareva will reach a career high No.2 in the rankings if she wins the Toray Pan Pacific title and will face  Agnieszka Radwanska in the final. Polish star Radwanska shocked third seed Victoria Azarenka 6-3 4-6 6-2 in the other semifinal. Ninth seed Radwanska led 6-3 4-2 until Azarenka launched a fight back to win the second set, but two breaks of service saw her home in the decider on her fourth match point. Zvonareva looked in big trouble in the opening stages of her match against Kvitova and faced three set points on her Czech opponent's service until winning it on a tiebreak. The second set was completely one-sided as she breezed into her 30th carrer final. \"I don't even remember being down 5-1 in the first set!\" Zvonareva told the WTA official website. \"But I slowly got into the match, making the shots I usually make. Then I was able to turn it around. \"I think I played very consistently in the second set and Petra started to make a few more mistakes. We had some tough games, but I was able to convert all my chances, and that's why the scoreline looked like that in the end.\" Despite the loss, Kvitova's run to the semifinal will lift her into the top five in the WTA rankings for the first time. Meanwhile, former world number one Maria Sharapova has pulled out of next week's China Open with an ankle injury she picked up in in her quarterfinal against Kvitova. The 24-year-old Russian was force to retire after twisting her ankle, but is hopeful she can return to the circuit before the end of the season. \"Will do my best to recover in time for Istanbul (the season-ending WTA Championships),\" Sharapova said on her website. On the men's ATP Tour, world number four Andy Murray breezed into the semifinals of the Thailand Open in Bangkok. The top seed beat Bulgaria's Grigor Dimitrov 6-4 6-4 in one hour and 28 minutes as he remained on course to win his third title of the season.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Russian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Vera Zvonareva",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "5",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Wimbledon",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Petra Kvitova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "7",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "6",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "WTA",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Tokyo",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Zvonareva",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Toray",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Pan Pacific",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Agnieszka Radwanska",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Polish",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Radwanska",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "third",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Victoria Azarenka",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "6",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "4",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Ninth",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Radwanska",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "6",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "4",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Azarenka",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "two",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "fourth",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Zvonareva",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kvitova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "three",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Czech",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "30th",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "5",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Zvonareva",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "WTA",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Petra",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kvitova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "five",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "WTA",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Maria Sharapova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "next week's",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "China Open",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Kvitova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "24-year-old",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Russian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Istanbul",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "WTA Championships",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Sharapova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "ATP Tour",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "four",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Andy Murray",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the Thailand Open",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Bangkok",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Bulgaria",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Grigor Dimitrov",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "6",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "6",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "one hour and 28 minutes",
          "TIME"
        ],
        [
          "third",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "the season",
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "Macedonia is a small landlocked country bordering Albania, Bulgaria, Greece, Kosovo and Serbia. About a quarter of its two million population lives in the capital Skopje, a city on the Vardar River brimming with evidence of a 2,500 year history that has seen it come under Roman, Byzantine, Ottoman and Yugoslav rule. The raging river divides the Albanian and Macedonian communities of Skopje. Almost two-thirds of the country's population are Orthodox Christians and a third is Muslim, according to the CIA World Factbook. As a result, the country has numerous monasteries, churches and mosques. It also plays host to a number of ancient relics dating back as far as 3,800 years. Lake Ohrid in the south west of the country -- one of the deepest and oldest lakes in Europe -- was once surrounded by 365 churches, some dating as far back as the 4th century. Macedonia lies in a seismically active region and has several hot thermal baths. There are many mountains over 2,500m in the Shar Planina range. The Lonely Planet travel guide describes the country as a \"paradise\" for outdoor types with numerous opportunities for skiing, hiking and climbing. Macedonia was the only country to emerge peacefully from the former Yugoslavia but 20 years later it still has an international identity crisis over its name. Macedonia gained independence from the former Yugoslav federation with overwhelming majority support in a referendum on September 8, 1991. To its own citizens, the country is called the Republic of Macedonia, but both the United Nations and the European Union call it the Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia (FYR Macedonia). The reason for the controversy is a region in Greece that is also called Macedonia. International recognition of Macedonia's independence was delayed by Greek objections to the name. Greece eventually agreed to recognize the \"former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia\" designation. Most Macedonians do not like this name, and negotiations are continuing under the United Nations to find a solution, according to the British Foreign and Commonwealth Office. In 2001, there was an uprising of ethnic Albanians -- who make up a quarter of the population -- demanding equal rights, leading to months of violence. Peace returned later the same year with a peacekeeping operation by NATO troops and a new constitution recognizing Albanian as an official language and increasing access for ethnic Albanians to public sector jobs, including the police force. Official statistics show high unemployment at 31.7 percent as of 2010, but this does not take into account the extensive informal job market, estimated to be more than 20 per cent of GDP, according to the CIA World Factbook. Macedonia's current president Gjorgje Ivanov came to power in elections in 2009. Prime Minister Nikola Gruevski meanwhile was re-elected in parliamentary elections held in July 2011. His conservative VMRO-DPMNE party now governs in coalition with the ethnic Albanian DUI party. In his victory speech, Ivanov claimed his main priority was seeking further integration and ties with Europe. Macedonia is currently a candidate for membership of the European Union. In September 2011 Macedonia celebrated its 20th anniversary as an independent state. To mark the occasion new monuments, museums, roads and an improved airport terminal were constructed. The centrepiece was the erection of a 24 meter high statue of Alexander the Great in Skopje's Macedonia Square. The monument has caused further friction with neighboring Greece who view the warrior king as a Greek rather than Macedonian national hero. Given that it is still a relatively young country; the number of Macedonians to have left their mark on the world stage is relatively small. Some the most notable include footballer Goran Pandev, who won the European Champions League in 2010 whilst playing for Italian giants Inter Milan, and filmmaker Milco Mancevski, who received an Oscar nomination for his 1995 picture \"Before the Rain.\" Humanitarian and Nobel peace prize winner Mother Teresa was also born in Skopje in 1910, although Macedonia was still part of the Ottoman Empire at this time.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Albania",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Bulgaria",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Greece",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Kosovo",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Serbia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "About a quarter",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "two million",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Skopje",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "the Vardar River",
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          "2,500 year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Roman",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Byzantine",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Ottoman",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Yugoslav",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Albanian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Skopje",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Almost two-thirds",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Orthodox Christians",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "a third",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Muslim",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "CIA",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "3,800 years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Lake Ohrid",
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Europe",
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          "365",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "the 4th century",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "over 2,500m",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "Shar Planina",
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          "Lonely Planet",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Yugoslavia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "20 years later",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Yugoslav",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "September 8, 1991",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "the Republic of Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "the United Nations",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "the European Union",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "the Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "FYR Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Greece",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Greek",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Greece",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonians",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "the United Nations",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "the British Foreign and Commonwealth Office",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2001",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Albanians",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "a quarter",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "months",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "later the same year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "NATO",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Albanian",
          "LANGUAGE"
        ],
        [
          "Albanians",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "31.7 percent",
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          "2010",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "more than 20 per cent",
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          "the CIA World Factbook",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Gjorgje Ivanov",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2009",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Nikola Gruevski",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "July 2011",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "VMRO-DPMNE",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Albanian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "DUI",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Ivanov",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Europe",
          "LOC"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "the European Union",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "September 2011",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "20th",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "24 meter",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "Alexander the Great",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Skopje",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia Square",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "Greece",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Greek",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonians",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Goran Pandev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the European Champions League",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2010",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Inter Milan",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Milco Mancevski",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Oscar",
          "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
          "1995",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Before the Rain",
          "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
          "Nobel peace prize",
          "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
          "Mother Teresa",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Skopje",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "1910",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Macedonia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "the Ottoman Empire",
          "GPE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "Manchester City banned journalists from asking manager Roberto Mancini about striker Carlos Tevez  Friday, as the fallout from the Argentine's apparent refusal to come on as a substitute continued. Tevez, 27, has been suspended pending an investigation by City after Italian manager Mancini claimed the forward refused to come on as a second-half substitute during City's 2-0 European Champions League defeat to Bayern Munich Tuesday. But the 2011 FA Cup winners refused to answer questions on the former Manchester United star during Mancini's press conference ahead of the club's English Premier League clash at Blackburn Rovers Saturday. \"Questions in relation to Carlos Tevez in general, in relation to his alleged conduct on Tuesday evening and the potential ramifications of that conduct and in relation to his future at the football club is strictly off limits and will not be answered,\" City's chief communications officer Victoria Kloss said. Is Tevez \"strike\" sad for soccer? \"Breaches of this will result in the press conference being suspended. This decision has been made to protect the interests of all parties and safeguard the integrity of the investigation that is currently taking place.\" Former Inter Milan coach Mancini rejected suggestions recent events had made this week the hardest of his 10-year managerial career. \"Why is it difficult?\" the 46-year-old said. \"Some situations can happen in football, in your job. It's important that the past is finished. I don't have any complications. \"Only one complication that we had two days ago is that we lost against Bayern Munich, only this. Tevez suspended by Manchester City \"We started very well we can do a fantastic season, I don't have this problem. It is normal that one player is not happy to leave the pitch in an important game or to stay on the bench, it's a normal situation for every manager.\" The defeat to German outfit Bayern was City's first of the season, with the Etihad Stadium outfit still unbeaten and sitting in second position after six games in England's top division. Later Friday, City rejected a request from second-flight West Ham to take Tevez on a temporary loan. Tevez played for the Hammers when he first arrived in English football, helping them to avoid relegation before moving to Manchester United. In addition to the controversy surrounding Tevez, City's reverse at the Allianz Arena also saw Bosnian striker Edin Dzeko react angrily to being replaced by Dutch midfielder Nigel de Jong in the second half. Dzeko, who arrived in Manchester from Bundesliga side Wolfsburg in January, has apologized for his actions and said they were born out of disappointment with his own performance. \"Everyone has had a sleep and a rest after the Bayern game and we know we could have done better but it is football and you cannot win every game,\" Dzeko, who has already scored six Premier League goals this season, told City's official website. \"Bayern Munich is behind us, we are feeling positive and looking forward to the next game. That is our target now. I know my reaction was bad and I have spoken to the guys and to the coach as well. \"I have apologized for the reaction and Roberto has accepted it and said that everything is ok and that we have to be positive for the next game.\" After Saturday's match at Ewood Park, City entertain Aston Villa on October 15 before Villarreal arrive in Manchester for a Champions League clash on October 18.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Manchester City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Roberto Mancini",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Carlos Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Argentine",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "27",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Mancini",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "2",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "European Champions League",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Bayern Munich",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Tuesday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "2011",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "FA Cup",
          "EVENT"
        ],
        [
          "Manchester United",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Mancini",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "English Premier League",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Blackburn Rovers",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Saturday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Carlos Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Tuesday evening",
          "TIME"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Victoria Kloss",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Inter Milan",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Mancini",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "this week",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "10-year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "46-year-old",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Only one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "two days ago",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Bayern Munich",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Manchester City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "German",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Bayern",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "the season",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Etihad Stadium",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "six",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "England",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Later Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "West Ham",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Hammers",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "English",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Manchester United",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Tevez",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "the Allianz Arena",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "Bosnian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Edin Dzeko",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Dutch",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Nigel de Jong",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Dzeko",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Manchester",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Bundesliga",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Wolfsburg",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "January",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Bayern",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Dzeko",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "six",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Premier League",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "this season",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Bayern Munich",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Roberto",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Saturday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Ewood Park",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "City",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Aston Villa",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "October 15",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Villarreal",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Manchester",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Champions League",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "October 18",
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "President Dmitry Medvedev said Friday he had ceded his presidency bid to the country's powerful Prime Minister Vladimir Putin because the latter is a more popular politician in Russia, who has higher chances to be elected.  \"Prime Minister Putin is definitely  the most authoritative politician in our country and his rating is somewhat higher (than mine),\" Medvedev said in a taped interview with Russia's national TV networks.  Public opinion polls in Russia have invariably indicated that Putin has been ahead of Medvedev in popularity ever since they constructed their ruling tandem almost four years ago. According to the most recent poll, conducted by independent Levada Center, the approval rating of Medvedev stood at 62 per cent in September, compared to Putin's 68 per cent.  In his Friday television interview Medvedev said that he and Putin belong to \"the same political force\" and have \"very close positions on all strategic and tactical issues\" and therefore shouldn't compete or quarrel.  \"Can we possibly imagine, for instance, (U.S. President) Barack Obama competing with (Secretary of State) Hillary Clinton?\" Medvedev asked. \"Both of them were bidding for the presidential nomination ... Both were from the Democratic Party, and (the party) finally decided which of them should run to gain the best election result. Our decision was the same,\" Medvedev said.  \"We want to achieve a political result, to win the elections -- the parliamentary elections in December and the presidential elections in March -- not to be nursing our ambitions,\" Medvedev said.  \"Any responsible person's ambition is to serve his country, and I insist on that,\" he said.  Commenting on the statements made by some people that the outcome of the Russian presidential elections is \"predetermined\", Medvedev said, \"I consider such statements absolutely irresponsible, deceitful, and even provocative.\"  \"The decisions made at the congress are only recommendations to the party to support two people in the elections, no more than that,\" he said.  Last Saturday Medvedev called on the ruling United Russia party to endorse Putin for president in 2012. Putin in turn suggested that Medvedev should take over the role of prime minister if the party wins parliamentary elections in December, in what would be a straight swap of their roles.  The announcement ended more than two years of speculation about whether Putin or Medvedev, his hand-picked successor, would seek to run for a second term.  Putin had stepped down as president in 2008 because the Russian constitution at that time limited the office to two consecutive four-year terms.  Under amendments to the constitution that came into force on December 31, 2008, the presidential term was extended to six years.  This means that if Putin is elected in March 2012 for six years, he would be eligible to run for another six-year term after that, potentially keeping him in charge until 2024. ",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Dmitry Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Vladimir Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Russia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Russia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Russia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "almost four years ago",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Levada Center",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "62 per cent",
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          "September",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "68 per cent",
          "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "U.S.",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Barack Obama",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "State",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Hillary Clinton",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the Democratic Party",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "December",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "March",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Russian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "two",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Last Saturday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "United Russia",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2012",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "December",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "more than two years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Medvedev",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "second",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2008",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Russian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "two",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "four-year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "December 31, 2008",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "six years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Putin",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "March 2012",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "six years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "six-year",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "2024",
          "DATE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "Prehistoric children as young as three were encouraged by adults to make cave art 13,000 years ago, new research shows. The Cambridge University study sheds new light on the lives of children and the ancient art they made during the prehistoric hunter gatherer period in the French caverns at Rouffignac, known as the Cave of a Hundred Mammoths. While the caverns are famous for their striking drawings of woolly mammoths, bison and horses, the research focused on the thousands of lines made by people running their fingers along the soft clay walls throughout the five mile cavern complex. Cambridge archaeologists were able to identify the age and gender of the children who made the simple ancient art form known as \"finger fluting\" by measuring the width of the flutings and the profile of the middle three fingers. \"We have found marks by children aged between three and seven years old -- and we have been able to identify four individual children by matching up their marks,\" said Cambridge University archaeologist Jess Cooney. \"The most prolific of the children who made flutings was aged around five -- and we are almost certain the child in question was a girl.\" The fact that archaeologists didn't find a single place where fluting marks were made by adults alone suggests there were few boundaries between adult and child activities in this prehistoric hunter gatherer culture, according to Cooney. Not only did the adults make art alongside the children, Cooney says the fact that child-sized flutings were found on the ceilings of some cave chambers means adults actively encouraged them to make art, lifting them up to areas they could not reach alone. \"Some of the children's flutings are high up on the walls and on the ceilings, so they must have been held up to make them or have been sitting on someone's shoulders,\" she said. The archaeologists believe one of the caverns is so dominated by children's flutings that it may actually have been a \"special place\" set aside for them by the adults. \"We sometimes think of one chamber as a playpen of sorts, since there are hundreds of children's flutings but only a few made by adults,\" said Cooney. Why people made finger flutings, which also appear in caves in Spain, New Guinea and Australia, is anyone's guess. \"We don't know why people made them. We can make guesses like they were for initiation rituals, for training of some kind, or simply something to do on a rainy day,\" said Cooney. The children weren't simply running their hands mindlessly along the cavern walls, however. Research in 2006 revealed children had made hut-like shapes called tectiforms -- the first known instance of prehistoric children engaging in symbolic figure-making, according to Cooney. Cooney says her research shines a light on an aspect of history that is typically ignored in academia. \"It's important to realize that children played a major role in the development of not only art, but what it means to be human,\" she said.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "three",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "13,000 years ago",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Cambridge University",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "French",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Rouffignac",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "the Cave of a Hundred Mammoths",
          "FAC"
        ],
        [
          "thousands",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "five mile",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "Cambridge",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "three",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "between three and seven years old",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "four",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Cambridge University",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Jess Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "five",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "hundreds",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Spain",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "New Guinea",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Australia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "a rainy day",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2006",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Cooney",
          "PERSON"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "Amanda Knox is the victim of prosecutors who have decided she is guilty \"regardless of logic and reason,\" her attorney said Friday during statements in the appeal of her 2009 murder conviction. Knox and former boyfriend, Rafaello Sollecito, are appealing their 2009 convictions for the death of Knox's former roommate, Meredith Kercher, whose body was found half-naked with her throat slashed on November 2, 2007. Prosecutors said in their statements Friday that evidence against the pair is clear, from bloody footprints with particular characteristics to the spot where Knox's DNA was found on a kitchen knife believed by investigators to be the murder weapon. \"They are young, but so was Meredith. They've murdered. And they have killed for nothing. And for this they must be condemned to the maximum sentence,\" Manuela Comodi said. But Knox's attorney, Maria Del Grosso, said her client is the victim of bad casting in a script in which prosecutors have decided she is guilty, \"regardless of the logic and reason.\" For the convictions to stand, Del Grosso argued, prosecutors need, \"proofs, proofs, proofs, and in this case there is only the proof that they are strangers to this crime.\" No ruling is expected until Monday, when Knox and Sollecito are expected to give final statements, according to the judge. Knox's father, Curt Knox, said he is hopeful his daughter will be able to return home soon. \"It has been a very hard journey and hopefully we're near the end of it,\" he said. Prosecutors claim Knox slashed Kercher's throat as Sollecito and a third defendant, Rudy Guede, held her down. Knox was sentenced to 26 years in prison, while Sollecito got 25. Guede was convicted in a separate trial and is serving 16 years. Knox and Sollecito's defense teams have suggested Guede could have been the sole killer and argue the police investigation was shoddy and incomplete. Del Grosso said there was no evidence of a cover-up attempt, as prosecutors claim, and accused prosecutors of using a double standard when it comes to evidence in the case. Sollecito's lawyer, Donatella Donati, told the court that her team suffered repeated roadblocks each time they asked for further reviews of the evidence and said it was clear that some of the evidence had been contaminated. On Thursday, defense attorneys argued Knox had been denied a translator and was discouraged from getting a lawyer when she was arrested, and portrayed her as a young girl, inexperienced with world travel and unable to speak Italian. Knox's attorneys also argued for the exclusion of some DNA evidence in the case, including evidence of blood that prosecutors said belonged to both women found in a bathroom they shared and evidence from the knife, which Knox attorney Carlo Dalla Vedova on Thursday called a \"concentration of nothingness, a fantasy.\" Friday morning, prosecutor Giuliano Mignini said Knox and Sollecito tried to blame the killing on Guede because Guede is black. Comodi showed jurors a photograph of a bloody footprint found in the bathroom of the home were Kercher was killed. There was no way the footprint was Guede's as defense attorneys had contended, Comodi argued. She said experts have concluded that the footprint was not Guede's and probably was Sollecito's. She also told the court that just because the footprint was found \"not usable\" for positive identification, it doesn't mean that they are \"non usable'\" when you can do a process of elimination. Comodi also used her microphone to demonstrate how the location where Knox's DNA was found on the presumed murder weapon -- at the junction between the blade and the handle -- suggests a stabbing motion, rather than a cutting motion. Also Friday, Carlo Pacelli, the attorney for Patrick Lumumba -- who was initially accused in the case -- called Knox a \"mixed concentration of sex, drugs and alcohol\"  who, despite the portrait painted by defense attorneys, was a \"diabolical defamer.\" Lumumba, the former owner of a bar where Knox worked, sued Knox for libel. In the Italian court system, criminal and civil portions of a case are heard in the same proceeding.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Amanda Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "2009",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Rafaello Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2009",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Meredith Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "November 2, 2007",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Meredith",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Manuela Comodi",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Maria Del Grosso",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Del Grosso",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Monday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Curt Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "third",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Rudy Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "26",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "25",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "16 years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Del Grosso",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Donatella Donati",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Thursday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Carlo Dalla Vedova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Thursday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "morning",
          "TIME"
        ],
        [
          "Giuliano Mignini",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Comodi",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Comodi",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Comodi",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Friday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Carlo Pacelli",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Patrick Lumumba",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Lumumba",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "France is to open an office in North Korea in the coming days to build cultural ties and help with aid efforts, the French Foreign Ministry said Thursday. The creation of this office responds to \"a decision made by French authorities that takes into consideration identified cultural and humanitarian needs,\" a statement from the minister of foreign affairs' office said. The Office of French Cooperation in Pyongyang will be directed by diplomat and cultural cooperation expert Olivier Vaysset, the statement said. \"His goal will be to help the North Korean people, who are hit hard by many different kinds of restrictions, and to continue our cooperation activities in the domains of language, education and culture,\" it said. U.N. Secretary General Ban Ki-moon met with Pak Gil Yon, vice foreign minister for North Korea, on Wednesday, his office said. The pair discussed food shortages and related humanitarian problems in the North Korea, particularly since recent floods, the statement said. Ban said more international aid was needed and urged North Korea to improve its cooperation with U.N. agencies to help that happen. He also urged continued dialogue on the issue of North Korea's nuclear ambitions.",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "France",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "North Korea",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "the coming days",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "the French Foreign Ministry",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Thursday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "French",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "The Office of French Cooperation",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Pyongyang",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Olivier Vaysset",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "North Korean",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "U.N.",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Ban Ki-moon",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Pak Gil Yon",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "North Korea",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Wednesday",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "North Korea",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Ban",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "North Korea",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "U.N.",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "North Korea's",
          "GPE"
        ]
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "body": "There was a plane ticket from Perugia, Italy, to Seattle, Washington, with Amanda Knox's name on it. Her parents bought it in the hope that Knox would be home for Christmas. They bought it as a leap of faith, hoping she would be legally vindicated of the allegation that she killed her roommate Meredith Kercher. They were tired of seeing their daughter's name plastered across newspapers around the world with the word murderer alongside it. But the ticket was never used.  In December 2009, that ticket got shredded along with some of the hope her family was clinging to as she was hauled away as a convicted murderer from an Italian court. Now, as closing arguments in Amanda Knox's appeal come to an end, one thing remains the same for the Knox parents: A plane ticket home. They just hope they'll be able to use it this time. A fight to clear Amanda Knox's name In 2009, Curt Knox and Edda Mellas (they divorced in 1989) boarded a plane to Italy for the verdict in their daughter's murder trial. Hope pumped through their veins: a hope that an Italian court would see that their daughter was not a murderer. They were fighting a legal battle in which the odds were stacked unfairly against their daughter, according to many in Knox's camp. They were also fighting to preserve their daughter's image by countering what they felt was an unfair media caricature of their daughter as \"Foxy Knoxy.\" The nickname, her parents said, was given to her in school because of her soccer skills, but during the murder trial it became a nickname to portray her as a careless, sex-crazed party girl. Her family told the story of an entirely different Amanda Knox: one who was \"nonviolent\" and \"almost a passive person.\"Amanda Knox: From Seattle to Italy Prosecutors alleged at trial that on the night of November 1, 2007, at a small house in the college town of Perugia, Knox directed her then-boyfriend Rafaelle Sollecito and a third defendant Rudy Guede, to hold Kercher down as Knox played with a knife before slashing Kercher's throat. They said the trio left her in a pool of blood and covered her with her own blanket. Knox's parents, like her defense attorneys, said their daughter was not involved in the murder and that evidence presented at trial was thin and clouded by shoddy police work. But at the trial, those arguments fell on deaf ears. Knox was convicted along with Sollecito in the murder of Kercher and sentenced to 26 and 25 years respectively. Guede was convicted in a separate fast-track trial and is serving 16 years in prison. Now, two years after Knox's conviction, Knox's parents are fighting a similar battle during her appeal. Finding 'the truth' of what happened in Perugia Inside the same Italian courtroom where Knox and Sollecito were convicted and sentenced, they now fight to try and prove the court got it all wrong. The dispute over forensic evidence has prompted many Knox supporters to question how the Italian court arrived at a conviction. Gallery: A look at the evidence \"From what we have heard (about) first trials here in Italy, a lot of it is related to emotion,\" Curt Knox told CNN earlier this month. And he, like many in the Knox camp, wonders why more wasn't done to clarify facts about the evidence at trial in order to avoid his daughter being convicted and imprisoned for two years and 24 more to go. \"When you look at the actual forensic evidence (from the murder trial) -- when you take a look at what the police were saying, which is literally 180 degrees different than what the defense was saying about the forensic evidence, and not have an independent review during the first trial, you can see how the result came out as is,\" he said. Disputed evidence at the heart of appeal Attorneys for Knox and Sollecito, are appealing their convictions together since they were tried and convicted together. Timeline of the Knox case An independent forensic investigation they fought for at trial could help overturn the convictions in the appeal, the attorneys said. During the murder trial, defense attorneys challenged key DNA evidence found on the alleged murder weapon, a knife, and on Kercher's bra clasp, arguing it had been contaminated after being left for weeks at the crime scene.. They asked for an independent examination of the evidence, but it was denied. During the appeals process the independent examination was allowed and has become the central issue of the appeal. At trial in 2009 prosecutors said there were traces of Knox's genetic material on the knife handle and traces of Kercher's in a tiny groove on the blade. That DNA was used to tie Knox to the crime scene during the murder trial, though defense attorneys argued there was barely enough DNA to get an accurate reading. During the appeal, one of the independent forensic experts who studied the original evidence told the court that the DNA alleged to be Kercher's that was on the knife could not have been from blood. That key statement has led to a defense argument that there is now truly no official evidence that links Knox to the scene. The next battle in the appeal was to dismiss evidence that prosecutors said ties Sollecito to the murder scene. At trial, the prosecution said a bra clasp found on the bloodied crime scene floor had Sollecito's DNA on it and proved he was in Kercher's room when the murder occurred. Defense attorneys argued the bra clasp had been left on the floor for nearly six weeks before it was collected and was likely contaminated. In the appeal, two independent forensic experts argued Sollecito DNA allegedly found on the bra clasp should be \"inadmissible\" because the clasp had not been properly handled. Prosecutors dismissed the theory again during the appeal, specifying it had been moved but not turned over or stepped on at the scene. They said documents showed that proper checks were carried out before and after their DNA tests to verify the quality of the work. But the appeals judge couldn't find the documents in court records and ruled they would not be admissible. The appeals judge denied prosecution efforts to introduce newly found records about the original testing and to hear a new witness -- all victories for Knox's defense, which opposed the motions. Curt Knox said he feels there is \"no case left\" against his daughter. And that's something he said his daughter is clinging to. Will Knox return to prison -- or back home to Seattle? The DNA evidence is the primary subject of closing arguments on both sides of the appeal. Prosecutor Manuela Comodi refuted the testimony from independent forensics experts that cast doubt on the reliability of the evidence, insisting police forensic officers had handled the DNA material properly. She cast doubt on one of the expert who was a professor, rather than a professional in the field and said police had better experience when it came to processing the crime scene than an independent expert. The review had been \"embarrassing, inappropriate, and presented in a hostile way\" and was not based on science, she said. Before asking the jurors to uphold the conviction she told them that the original court had concluded \"beyond any reasonable doubt\" that blood from both Knox and Kercher found in the bathroom sink had been left there when Knox washed herself after the killing. Prosecutor Giuliano Mignini, who investigated the original murder and defended the prosecution's case in the appeal, urged the jurors to make their decision on the basis of what they had heard in court, not in the overwhelming media coverage. But Knox and Sollecito's defense teams are arguing the whole trial was based on DNA evidence \"on which mistakes were made,\" and urged the jury to \"abandon imagined fantasies\" and acquit the pair. Sollecito's defense lawyer Giulia Bongiorno also said during closing arguments to remember that the true evidence points to who they believe is the sole killer: Rudy Guede. Guede, who was convicted earlier of the crime, has admitted being in the villa where Kercher was killed, but has said an unknown assailant killed her while he was out of the room during his trial. He later implicated Knox and Sollecito. During his trial prosecutors introduced evidence that showed Guede's handprint in Kercher's blood was found in the room along with his DNA inside her body as well as on her clothing and on her purse. \"The room speaks only of Rudy,\" Bongiorno said during closing arguments. Bongiorno also attacked the media portrayal of Knox as a \"femme fatale,\" which he said swayed the outcome of the trial. Knox's lawyer, Carlo Dalla Vedova, said the court had already seen \"there is not trace of Amanda Knox in the room where murder took place.\" He told the jury based on the evidence \"that the only possible decision to take is that of absolving Amanda Knox.\" Speculation is rampant as to whether defense attorneys have cast doubt on the evidence that sent Sollecito and Knox to prison for murder. Even the prosecutor's office told CNN that its attorneys are less certain of the outcome this time. The prosecution is still confident that the verdict will be upheld, but is aware that it could go either way, the office said. Curt Knox is more hopeful. \"It really appears to me that they want to find the truth,\" he said during the appeal. \"I'm very hopeful that by the end of the month, we'll be able to bring Amanda and Rafaelle home.\"",
    "entities": {
      "entities": [
        [
          "Perugia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Italy",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Seattle",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Washington",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda Knox's",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Christmas",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Meredith Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "December 2009",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda Knox's",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda Knox's",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "2009",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Curt Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Edda Mellas",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "1989",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Italy",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Foxy Knoxy",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "\"Amanda Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Seattle",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Italy",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "the night of November 1,",
          "TIME"
        ],
        [
          "Perugia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Rafaelle Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "third",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Rudy Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "26 and",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "25 years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "16 years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "two years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Perugia",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Italian",
          "NORP"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Italy",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Curt Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "CNN",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "earlier this month",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "two years",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "24",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "180 degrees",
          "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
          "first",
          "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "weeks",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "2009",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "nearly six weeks",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "two",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Curt Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Seattle",
          "GPE"
        ],
        [
          "Manuela Comodi",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "one",
          "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Giuliano Mignini",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Giulia Bongiorno",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Rudy Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Guede",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Kercher",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Rudy",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Bongiorno",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Bongiorno",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Carlo Dalla Vedova",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Sollecito",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "CNN",
          "ORG"
        ],
        [
          "Curt Knox",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "the end of the month",
          "DATE"
        ],
        [
          "Amanda",
          "PERSON"
        ],
        [
          "Rafaelle",
          "PERSON"
        ]
      ]
    }
  }
]